<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dungeons and Gatherers</title>
    <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dungeons and Gatherers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dragonfly Wings and Horse Teeth</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/dragonfly-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/dragonfly-wings/</guid>
      <description>The Non-Diddling Adventurers (NDA) decide to leave the Lost Property hut and head toward the carousel. However, on their way there, they are confronted by a group of bandits wearing coveted dragonfly wings. The bandits, a motely crew of toughs with missing teeth/eyes, a mohawk, and several piercings, including a Prince Albert, are led by an unnamed thug wearing a deep V-neck shirt. The leader tells the NDA to give up all their money, otherwise the thugs will take it by force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the Carnival</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/into-the-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/into-the-carnival/</guid>
      <description>Drawn by a nagging pull to recover something each of them had lost as a child, our group of adventurers finds themselves waiting in line to enter the Witchlight Carnival, a spectacle of lights, magic, and merriment. While in line, the adventurers discuss their favorite crab rangoon recipes and introduce themselves as:
Korv Brothbringer, Ankor Black, Strowkin Ahn, Renis Ratman, Tun the Toothgrabber, and Yendar Starpyre When it&amp;rsquo;s finally their turn to purchase tickets, the adventurers are greeted by Nikolas Midnight, an elderly goblin, who informs the party that a mysterious patron has already purchased tickets for the group &amp;ndash; although he&amp;rsquo;s pretty sure one of the tickets is supposed to go to a &amp;ldquo;Penis Patman&amp;rdquo; and not Renis Ratman.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
