<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dungeons and Gatherers</title>
    <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dungeons and Gatherers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Will Be Ruthless</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/ruthless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/ruthless/</guid>
      <description>Having successfully defeated (well, sort of) Bavlorna Blightstraw, member of the Hourglass Coven and ruler of Downfall, the NDA find themselves ganking items out of her frog-statue-treasure-hoard, including 6 glamerweave cloaks as well as a handful of leaves, which Renis promptly pockets. And thanks to a flying kick from Korv, they also manage to bust open a locked treasure chest that contains a creepy-looking (but nonmagical) marionette and an unpunched ticket to the Witchlight Carnival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS Paint Cartography</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/ms-paint-cartography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/ms-paint-cartography/</guid>
      <description>After escaping a (well-deserved) whomping from Charles Barkless, the gang finally enters Bavlorna’s cottage in the middle of Downfall’s murky lake. Upon climbing the stairs, the NDA find themselves in a large room dominated by a pool of stagnant, stinky water. Ankor pokes around the room and finds nothing really of value, but he does notice that Bavlorna is only 20 pages into the first Harry Potter book. While Ankor is rifling through Bavlorna’s bookshelf, Strowkin looks down into the well in the middle of the pool that’s probably supposed to be bringing in fresh (well, as fresh as it can be from the murky lake) water and notices that it’s being blocked by a gelatinous cube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Barkless</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/charles-barkless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/charles-barkless/</guid>
      <description>After returning from a brief foray into the North Pole (where the NDA saved Santa from being possessed by some baddy from another dimension), the party finds themselves back in King Gullop XIX’s court, having just been slipped a message to seek out Illig, the Baron of Muckstump, to join the revolution.
Continuing their circuit around the lake in the middle of Downfall, the NDA stumbles across a group of cages, one of which is occupied by a Morgort, the Knight of Warts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Skin is In These Balloons?</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/skin-balloons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/skin-balloons/</guid>
      <description>The session begins with the NDA trying to cross over a section of the lake in the middle of Downfall via a series of rocks, only to find that one of the rocks is actually a Galeb Duhr named Rocky. After some debate and a forced apology, Rocky agrees to help the party cross the lake in exchange for either an attractive statue or a “big titty chia pet” to be delivered to him at a later date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I Have More Crawfish?</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/more-crawfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/more-crawfish/</guid>
      <description>After defeating Agdon Longscarf, the leader of the harengon brigands and brander of baby-rapers everywhere, a cooling breeze swept through the NDA, and they felt stronger…almost as if they had leveled up.
But it wasn’t all improved ability scores for the adventurers, as Korv and Angkor had to figure out how to remove the slanderous “baby raper” brands imparted upon them by Agdon. They settled upon pouring acid upon their affected body parts, which is, you know, certainly one approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agdon Longscarf</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/agdon-longscarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/agdon-longscarf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korv Loadbringer</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/korv-loadbringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/korv-loadbringer/</guid>
      <description>After recovering from their fits of sneezing and choking, the NDA take the opportunity to further question Sir Talavar. The little purple faerie dragon tells them his backstory – that he is an ambassador of the Seelie Court and the Summer Queen who had come to Prismeer to recruit Zybylna as an ally against the Seelie Court’s sworn enemies, the fomorians. However, upon arriving in Prismeer, Sir T discovered that the Hourglass Coven – the trio of Bavlorna, Skabatha, and Endelyn – had used Iggwilv’s Cauldron to freeze time in Zybylna’s palace and take control of Prismeer for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spongitelli&#39;s Pizza</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/spongitellis-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/spongitellis-pizza/</guid>
      <description>Trekking in the direction of the balloon crash, accompanied by Chet Chadly and the giant snail, the NDA finds themselves in the middle of a swamp, whose waters rise quickly and force the smaller members of the party to seek refuge, either on the shoulders of their friends or on Tensor’s Floating Disk. Tall enough to keep their heads above water, Korv and Strowkin continue wading through the swamp. However, unable to see the ground beneath their feet, they walk straight into a pit of quicksand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit People</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/rabbit-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/rabbit-people/</guid>
      <description>Emerging from the mirror portal, the (now level 3) adventurers find themselves in Prismeer, high atop a broken bridge. Upon regaining their composure, Korv, Strowkin, and Rictus all felt a strange sensation in their guts that the possessions they had lost as children were in this place. But they weren’t quite sure where or how to get them back.
Nevertheless, at the edge of the bridge they found a chest full of treats (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shit Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/shit-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/shit-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>After winning the cupcake-eating contest and spewing vomit on their fellow carnival-goers, the NDA treks back across the grounds to meet up with Burly, who&amp;rsquo;s been instructed to take them to meet with Mr. Witch and Mr. Light. On the way, Mr. Bells reminds them of his &amp;ldquo;plan&amp;rdquo; to steal Mr. Light&amp;rsquo;s scepter, which gives him insight into the moods of all of the carnival&amp;rsquo;s attendees, and which Mr. Bells wants to use as a bargaining chip to gain information about Prismeer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Fish or Bottom Fish?</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/top-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/top-fish/</guid>
      <description>After convincing Mr. Bells to return Candlefoot’s voice, the NDA discuss how they might steal Mr. Light’s magical witchlight scepter to gain leverage over the carnival owners. However, much to their chagrin, Mr. Bells doesn’t have any actual plan for how to get the scepter. He does, however, tell the adventurers that Mr. Witch and Mr. Light mostly hang out in their wagon in the staff area, which is surrounded by impassable magic thorns that only part for verified carnival staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoagie Fest</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/hoagie-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/hoagie-fest/</guid>
      <description>After conquering the carousel puzzle and flirting (or trying to flirt) with Diana, the NDA decide to head toward the dragonfly ride. However, on their way there, they spot the mysterious little girl with the pig mask along with a strangely nimble toad-like creature in the crowd. Feeling themselves as a result of their carousel successes, the group tries to pursue and capture the toad-like creature, which, it turns out, doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to be captured and is fast as fuck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragonfly Wings and Horse Teeth</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/dragonfly-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/dragonfly-wings/</guid>
      <description>The Non-Diddling Adventurers (NDA) decide to leave the Lost Property hut and head toward the carousel. However, on their way there, they are confronted by a group of bandits wearing coveted dragonfly wings. The bandits, a motely crew of toughs with missing teeth/eyes, a mohawk, and several piercings, including a Prince Albert, are led by an unnamed thug wearing a deep V-neck shirt. The leader tells the NDA to give up all their money, otherwise the thugs will take it by force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the Carnival</title>
      <link>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/into-the-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dungeons-and-gatherers.netlify.app/posts/into-the-carnival/</guid>
      <description>Drawn by a nagging pull to recover something each of them had lost as a child, our group of adventurers finds themselves waiting in line to enter the Witchlight Carnival, a spectacle of lights, magic, and merriment. While in line, the adventurers discuss their favorite crab rangoon recipes and introduce themselves as:
Korv Brothbringer, Ankor Black, Strowkin Ahn, Renis Ratman, Tun the Toothgrabber, and Yendar Starpyre When it&amp;rsquo;s finally their turn to purchase tickets, the adventurers are greeted by Nikolas Midnight, an elderly goblin, who informs the party that a mysterious patron has already purchased tickets for the group &amp;ndash; although he&amp;rsquo;s pretty sure one of the tickets is supposed to go to a &amp;ldquo;Penis Patman&amp;rdquo; and not Renis Ratman.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
